Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG.42.5
New York University Archives
- Series III: Oversize, 1963-2011; 212382
  - Hujar -- Press, 1990 October; 212428 (Box III:5, File 3)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Notes, Undated; 212427 (Box III:5, File 4)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Printed Materials and Clippings, 1989-1991; 212426 (Box III:5, File 5)
  - Etruscan Exhibition, 1988-1990; 212425 (Box III:5, File 6)
  - Zuka - The French Revolution Through American Eyes (Small Gallery), 1989; 212424 (Box III:5, File 7)
  - Excommunication, 1989 March 3-9; 212423 (Box III:5, File 8)
  - Anyone in New York -- Exhibition (Catalog), 1993; 212422 (Box III:6, Folder 1)
  - Anyone in New York -- Public Relations, 1993 December-1994 August; 212421 (Box III:6, Folder 2)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Research and Exhibition Materials, Circa 1991-1992; 212420 (Box III:6, Folder 3)
  - Brazilian Exhibition -- Regina Silveira and Nelson Leirner, Circa 1990-1991; 212419 (Box III:6, Folder 4)
  - Arne Svenson (Windows), Circa 1991-1992; 212418 (Box III:6, Folder 5)
  - Three Women in Black (Windows), Circa 1993-1994; 212417 (Box III:6, Folder 6)
  - Todd Watts -- Exhibition, Circa 1993-1994; 212416 (Box III:6, Folder 7)
  - Jason Reed (Small Gallery and Windows), 1995; 212415 (Box III:6, Folder 8)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Exhibition, Circa 1994-1995; 212414 (Box III:6, Folder 9)
  - Rene Santos -- Exhibition, Circa 1992-1994; 212413 (Box III:6, Folder 10)
  - Willie Doherty -- Exhibition, 1994; 212412 (Box III:6, Folder 11)
  - Mark Beard (Windows), 1995; 212411 (Box III:6, Folder 12)
  - Mark Beard (Windows), Undated; 212410 (Box III:6, Folder 13)
  - Adrian Piper -- Decide Who You Are, Circa 1991-1992; 212409 (Box III:6, Folder 14)
  - Camera As Weapon, Circa 1992; 212408 (Box III:6, Folder 15)
  - Opulent Past -- Installation, Circa 1992; 212407 (Box III:6, Folder 16)
  - Bill Jacobson (Small Gallery), 1993 November 1; 212406 (Box III:7, Folder 1)
  - Space Photography -- Image Requests (JPL), 1981; 212405 (Box III:7, Folder 2)
  - Umbria Press, 1988-1989; 212404 (Box III:7, Folder 3)
  - Life -- Bookings (No Response or Rejections), Circa 1979; 212403 (Box III:7, Folder 4)
  - NetherArt -- Correspondence, 1992-1993; 212402 (Box III:7, Folder 5)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Press/Literature, 1981; 212401 (Box III:7, Folder 6)
  - Tanya Grosman -- Dinner, Circa 1981; 212400 (Box III:7, Folder 7)
  - American Symbolist -- Pivar Notes, Circa 1978-1979; 212399 (Box III:7, Folder 8)
  - Space Photography -- Life Magazine, 1981 June; 212398 (Box III:7, Folder 9)
  - Judson Dance Theater -- Poster, Circa 1980-1982; 212397 (Box III:7, Folder 10)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration -- Andre Kertesz, Circa 1980-1981; 212396 (Box III:7, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Press, 1988-1989; 212395 (Box III:7, Folder 12)
  - Jean Cocteau -- Paris, 1984 May; 212394 (Box III:8, Folder 1)
  - Show and Tell, Circa 1988; 212393 (Box III:8, Folder 2)
  - Robert Morris -- Catalog, Circa 1988-1990; 212392 (Box III:8, Folder 3)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Press, 1996; 212391 (Box III:8, Folder 4)
  - NetherArt, 1993; 212390 (Box III:8, Folder 5)
  - Space Photography -- Catalog, Circa 1980-1981; 212389 (Box III:8, Folder 6)
  - Tracking the Marvelous -- Catalog (John Myers Essay), 1981; 212388 (Box III:8, Folder 7)
  - Krasner/Pollock -- Brochure, 1981; 212387 (Box III:8, Folder 8)
  - Rosalind Solomon: Portraits in the Time of Aids -- Catalog, 1987-1988; 212386 (Box III:8, Folder 9)
  - Touching North -- Book, 1989; 212385 (Box III:8, Folder 10)
  - Judson Dance Theater -- Bennington College, Undated; 212384 (Box III:8, Folder 11)
  - Burra and Nash -- Works Requested, Undated; 212383 (Box III:8, Folder 12)
  - Documentation re items from "Triangle Fire Exhibition offered to NYU Archives", 2011 (Box III:8, Folder 13)
- Series IV: Publications, 1960-2020; 212288
  This series contains printed catalogs and other publications used by the gallery.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Undated Catalogs, 212381 (Box IV:1, Folder 1)
  - NYU Art Collection, 1960-1975; 212380 (Box IV:1, Folder 2)
  - NYU Art Collection, 1967-1973; 212379 (Box IV:1, Folder 3)
  - "Contemporary South West Asian-North African Graphics", 1969; 212378 (Box IV:1, Folder 4)
  - Abby Weed Grey, 1970-1976; 212377 (Box IV:1, Folder 5)
  - Catalogs, 1976-1978; 212376 (Box IV:1, Folder 6)
  - Catalogs, 1976-1979; 212375 (Box IV:1, Folder 7)
  - "American Painting: The Eighties", 1979; 212374 (Box IV:1, Folder 8)
  - "Life: The First Decade", 1979; 212373 (Box IV:1, Folder 9)
  - Catalogs, 1980; 212372 (Box IV:1, Folder 10)
  - "Italian Drawings 1780-1890" (1981), 1980; 212371 (Box IV:1, Folder 11)
  - Catalogs, 1980-1981; 212370 (Box IV:1, Folder 12)
  - "Judson Dance Theater: 1962-1966" (1982), 1981; 212369 (Box IV:1, Folder 13)
  - "Tracking the Marvelous", 1981; 212368 (Box IV:1, Folder 24)
  - Catalogs, 1981-1982; 212367 (Box IV:1, Folder 14)
  - Catalogs, 1982; 212366 (Box IV:1, Folder 15)
  - Abby Weed Grey Autobiography, 1983; 212365 (Box IV:1, Folder 16)
  - Catalogs, 1983; 212364 (Box IV:1, Folder 17)
  - Catalogs, 1984; 212363 (Box IV:1, Folder 18)
  - Catalogs, 1985; 212362 (Box IV:1, Folder 19)
  - Catalogs, 1986; 212361 (Box IV:1, Folder 20)
  - "Modern Redux", 1986; 212360 (Box IV:1, Folder 21)
  - Catalogs, 1987-1988; 212359 (Box IV:1, Folder 22)
  - "Cecil Beaton", 1988; 212358 (Box IV:1, Folder 23)
  - Catalogs, 1990-1991; 212357 (Box IV:2, Folder 1)
  - "Yasuzo Nojima and Contemporaries", 1991; 212356 (Box IV:2, Folder 2)
  - "Out of the Opulent Past", 1992; 212355 (Box IV:2, Folder 3)
  - Umbria, 1991; 212354 (Box IV:2, Folder 4)
  - Catalogs, 1992; 212353 (Box IV:2, Folder 5)
  - Catalogue, 1992-1993; 212352 (Box IV:2, Folder 6)
  - Catalogs, 1994-1995; 212351 (Box IV:2, Folder 7)
  - Catalogs, 1995; 212350 (Box IV:2, Folder 8)
  - "Traditions/Tensions: Contemporary Art in Asia", 1996; 212349 (Box IV:2, Folder 9)
  - "Philip Morris Art Award", 1996; 212348 (Box IV:2, Folder 10)
  - Catalogs and Publications, 1997; 212347 (Box IV:2, Folder 11)
  - Catalogs, 1997-1998; 212346 (Box IV:2, Folder 12)
  - "Rudy Burckhardt", 1998; 212345 (Box IV:2, Folder 13)
  - "Police Pictures: Photographs As Evidence", 1998; 212344 (Box IV:2, Folder 14)
  - "Philip Morris Award", 1998; 212343 (Box IV:2, Folder 15)
  - "Inverted Odysseys", 1999; 212342 (Box IV:2, Folder 16)
  - "When Time Began to Rant and Rage", 1999; 212341 (Box IV:2, Folder 17)
  - "Karel Teige/1900-1951" (2001), 1999; 212340 (Box IV:2, Folder 18)
  - "Face to Face", 2000; 212339 (Box IV:3, Folder 1)
  - "Images from Sheer Realities: Clothing and Power in Nineteenth Century Philippines", 2000; 212338 (Box IV:3, Folder 2)
  - "Ben Shah's New York", 2000; 212337 (Box IV:3, Folder 3)
  - "Shifting Tides: Cuban Photography After the Revolution", 2001; 212336 (Box IV:3, Folder 4)
  - Catalogs and Publications, 2001-2002; 212335 (Box IV:3, Folder 5)
  - "Zeitgenossische Fotokunst Aus Der Schweiz", 2002; 212334 (Box IV:3, Folder 6)
  - "The Park Avenue Cubists" (2003), 2002; 212333 (Box IV:3, Folder 7)
  - "Mapping Sitting: On Portraiture and Photography", 2002; 212332 (Box IV:3, Folder 8)
  - "Diane Arbus: Family Albums" (2004), 2003; 212331 (Box IV:3, Folder 9)
  - "Paul Kos", 2003; 212330 (Box IV:3, Folder 10)
  - "Erro", 2004; 212329 (Box IV:3, Folder 11)
  - "Modern American Painting from the NYU Art Collection", 2004; 212328 (Box IV:3, Folder 12)
  - "Ok/Okay", 2005; 212327 (Box IV:3, Folder 13)
  - "Paper Museums", 2005; 212326 (Box IV:3, Folder 14)
  - "The Downtown Book: The New York Art Scene 1974-1984", 2006; 212325 (Box IV:3, Folder 15)
  - "Lee Mullican: An Abundant Harvest of the Sun" (2006), 2005; 212324 (Box IV:3, Folder 16)
  - "Beyond the White Cube" (2007), 2006; 212323 (Box IV:3, Folder 17)
  - "Semina Culture" (2007), 212322 (Box IV:3, Folder 18)
  - "The Poetics of Cloth", 2008; 212321 (Box IV:3, Folder 19)
  - "New York Cool", 2008; 212320 (Box IV:4, Folder 1)
  - "John Wood: On the Edge of Clear Meaning" (2009), 2008; 212319 (Box IV:4, Folder 2)
  - "Damaged Romanticism" (2009), 2008; 212318 (Box IV:4, Folder 3)
  - "Artur Carter: Sculptures, Paintings, Drawings", 2009; 212317 (Box IV:4, Folder 4)
  - "Arthur Carter Sculpture and Drawings", 2009; 212316 (Box IV:4, Folder 5)
  - "John Storrs" (2011), 2010; 212315 (Box IV:4, Folder 6)
  - "Concrete Improvisations: Collages and Sculpture", 2011; 212314 (Box IV:4, Folder 7)
  - "Fluxus", 2011; 212313 (Box IV:4, Folder 8)
  - "Storied Past" Four Centuries of French Drawings from the Blanton Museum of Art", 2011; 212312 (Box IV:4, Folder 9)
  - "Sonia Delaunay", 1980; 212311 (Box IV:5)
  - "Perceiving Modern Sculpture: Selections for the Sighted and Non-Sighted", 1980; 212310 (Box IV:5)
  - "Contemporary Indian Art", 1985; 212309 (Box IV:5)
  - "Dreaming: The Gokstadt" (1990), 1985; 212308 (Box IV:5)
  - "The Lagoon Cycle" (1987), 1985; 212307 (Box IV:5)
  - "Morality Tales: History Painting in the 1980s", 1987; 212306 (Box IV:6)
  - "Awards in the Visual Arts 6", 1987; 212305 (Box IV:6)
  - "Success Is A Job In New York", 1989; 212304 (Box IV:6)
  - "Peter Hujar", 1990; 212303 (Box IV:6)
  - "Interrogating Identity", 1991; 212302 (Box IV:6)
  - "Anyone in New York", 1993; 212301 (Box IV:6)
  - "Suspension of the Law: Rene Santos, A Retrospective", 1994; 212300 (Box IV:6)
  - "Kazia", 1995; 212299 (Box IV:7)
  - "Nahum B. Zenil: Witness to the Self" (1997), 1996; 212298 (Box IV:7)
  - "Priceless Children: American Photographs 1890-1925" (2002), 2001; 212297 (Box IV:8)
  - "Seeing and Believing: The Art of Nancy Burson", 2002; 212296 (Box IV:8)
  - "Electrifying Art: Atsuko Tanaka 1954-1968", 2004; 212295 (Box IV:8)
  - "Moving Pictures: American Art and Early Film 1880-1910", 2005; 212294 (Box IV:8)
  - "The Geometry of Hope", 2007; 212293 (Box IV:9)
  - "Richard Diebenkorn in New Mexico", 2007; 212292 (Box IV:9)
  - "Kunstlerplakate der DDR 1967-1990", 2009; 212291 (Box IV:10)
  - "Icons of the Desert: Early Aboriginal Paintings from Papunya", 2009; 212290 (Box IV:10)
  - "Soto: Paris and Beyond 1950-1970", 2012; 212289 (Box IV:10)
  - "Ernest Cole, Photographer", 2010 (Box IV:11)
  - "Alice Aycock Drawings: Some Stories are Worth Repeating", 2013 (Box IV:11)
  - "Beat Memories: Photographs of Allen Ginsberg", 2010 (Box IV:11)
  - "Energy that is All Around: Mission School: Chris Johanson, Margaret Kilgallen, etc", 2014 (Box IV:11)
  - "Energy that is All Around: Happening at In Your Mind", limited edition catalog (179/250), undated (Box IV:11)
  - "Radical Presence: Black Performance in Contemporary Art", 2013 (Box IV:11)
  - "Toxic Beauty: The Art of Frank Moore", 2012 (Box IV:11)
  - "An Opening of the Field: Jess, Robert Duncan, and their Circle", 2013 (Box IV:11)
  - Leslie-Lohman's Art After Stonewall, 1969-1989 Special Edition of The Archive and Lapel Pins, 2019 (Box Shared University Archives 055, Folder 2)
  - "NeoRealismo: The New Image in Italy, 1932-1960", 2018 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - "The Expressionist: Fritz Ascher", 2019 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - "Metamorphoses: Ovid According to Wally Reinhardt", 2019 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - "Art After Stonewall, 1969-1989", 2019 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - "Modernisms: Iranian, Turkish, and Indian Highlights from NYU's Abby Weed Grey Collection", 2019 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - "Taking Shape: Abstraction from the Arab World, 1950s-1980s", 2020 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - "Anne Brigman: A Visionary in Modern Photography", 2020 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Series V: Photographs, 1964-1984; 242848; 10 Linear Feet in 20 manuscript boxes.
  This series contains photographic materials largely of and related to exhibitions hosted at the Grey Art Gallery.
  - The New York Painter, undated; 242842 (Box V:1, Folder 1)
  - The New York Painter, undated; 242843 (Box V:1, Folder 2)
  - Durand Ruel Exhibition: Photos, opening at Wildenstein, undated; 242844 (Box V:1, Folder 3)
  - Durand Ruel Exhibition: Photos/Wildenstein Benefit. (Stephanie Rancou), undated; 242845 (Box V:1, Folder 4)
  - Exhibition Photos: Concrete Expressionism, undated; 242846 (Box V:1, Folder 5)
  - Exhibition: Bernard Childs, 1964 April 14-May 15; 242847 (Box V:1, Folder 6)
  - Exhibitions -- Recent Acquisitions, 1966; 242849 (Box V:1, Folder 7)
  - University of Connecticut Exhibition Installation Photographs, 1973; 242850 (Box V:1, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, undated; 242852 (Box V:1, Folder 9)
  - Hudson River Museum Show Installation Photos, 1971 October 2-November 11; 242851 (Box V:2, Folder 1)
  - Loeb Show Photos, 1973 June-August; 242853 (Box V:2, Folder 2)
  - Notre Dame Installation Photos, 1973 January 14-February 25; 242854 (Box V:2, Folder 3)
  - Irish Directions of the 70s Photographs, 1975; 242855 (Box V:2, Folder 4)
  - Gallatin Photographs, undated; 242856 (Box V:2, Folder 5)
  - Gallery of Living Art Revisited Philadelphia Museum Corr., undated; 242857 (Box V:2, Folder 6)
  - Gallatin Photographs, undated; 242858 (Box V:2, Folder 7)
  - Selections from the NYU Collection, 1968 April 27-May 4; 242859 (Box V:2, Folder 8)
  - Abby Grey's Honorary Dinner, undated; 242871 (Box V:2, Folder 9)
  - Circa 1776 / Salute Press Photos, undated; 242872 (Box V:2, Folder 10)
  - Hudson River Museum Exhibition Benefit Reception (1 of 2), 1971 October 3 (Box V:2, Folder 11)
  - Hudson River Museum Exhibition Benefit Reception (2 of 2), 1971 October 3; 242860 (Box V:3, Folder 1)
  - NYU Art Exhibition Benefit, 1967; 242873 (Box V:3, Folder 2)
  - Report from SoHo Photographs, undated; 242874 (Box V:3, Folder 3)
  - Recent American Etching Photographs, undated; 242875 (Box V:3, Folder 4)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Photo Negatives (1 of 3), undated; 242878 (Box V:4, Folder 1)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Photo Negatives (2 of 3), undated; 242879 (Box V:4, Folder 2)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Photo Negatives (3 of 3), undated; 242880 (Box V:4, Folder 3)
  - Beatrix Potter -- National Trust Correspondence, 1977; 242881 (Box V:4, Folder 4)
  - Avedisian/Hennessy Essays by Christopher Scott, undated; 242882 (Box V:4, Folder 5)
  - Parviz Tanavoli/Locks from Iran -- Clipping File, undated; 242883 (Box V:4, Folder 6)
  - Marjorie Strider Big Box PR, undated; 242884 (Box V:4, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Poster Exhibition PR, undated; 242885 (Box V:4, Folder 8)
  - Aspects of American Realism Clippings, undated; 242886 (Box V:4, Folder 9)
  - Parviz Tanavoli -- Press Photos and Negatives, undated; 242887 (Box V:4, Folder 10)
  - Sandman -- Black and White Photos, undated; 242888 (Box V:4, Folder 11)
  - Restricted Series II: Development: Panoramic Photography Lenders M-Z, undated; 242889 (Box V:4, Folder 12)
  - Restricted Series II: Development: Panoramic Photography Lenders L- (2 of 2), undated; 242890 (Box V:4, Folder 13)
  - Beatrix Potter Press Releases (1 of 3), undated; 242891 (Box V:5, Folder 1)
  - Beatrix Potter Press Releases (2 of 3), undated; 242892 (Box V:5, Folder 2)
  - Beatrix Potter Press Releases (3 of 3), undated; 242893 (Box V:5, Folder 3)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Hunt Institute and Other Miscellaneous Photos, undated; 242894 (Box V:5, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Balet/Palmer/Smyth Press Photos, undated; 242895 (Box V:5, Folder 5)
  - House of Iran Exhibit, undated; 242896 (Box V:5, Folder 6)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright Documents/Objects -- Wright Rugs, undated; 242897 (Box V:5, Folder 7)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright Photographs, undated; 242898 (Box V:5, Folder 8)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright Press Photographs, undated; 242899 (Box V:5, Folder 9)
  - Wilmarth Black/White Photos, undated; 242900 (Box V:5, Folder 10)
  - Panoramic Photography -- Press Photos/Negatives, undated; 242901 (Box V:5, Folder 11)
  - Panoramic Photography, undated; 242902 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Assorted Audubon Reprints, undated; 242903 (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
  - Series I: Bill Komosky, undated; 242904 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Around the Square -- Old Photographs, undated; 242905 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Around the Square -- M. Feldstein Press Photos, undated; 242906 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Edward Henderson, 1981-1982; 242907 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Tiffany Bulletin, undated; 242908 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Tiffany Photos, undated; 242909 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Tiffany Color Transparencies, undated; 242910 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Hare/Kiesler Press Photos, undated; 242911 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Audubon Photographs, undated; 242912 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Series I: Audubon Negatives (1 of 2), undated; 242913 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Audubon Negatives (2 of 2), undated; 242914 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography -– Winokur (Press Only), undated; 242915 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Faces Photographed –- Steve Steigman (Press Only), undated; 242916 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Faces Photographed –- Bruce Weber (Press Only), undated; 242917 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography -– Cosimo di Leo Ricatto (Press Only), undated; 242918 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Faces Photographed -– Nan Goldin (Press Only), undated; 242919 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography -– Mapplethorpe, undated; 242920 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Faces Photographed –- K. McGowin, undated; 242921 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography -– Coupon, undated; 242922 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Morse -- Lucretia Walker Morse, undated; 242923 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Morse -- Marquis de Lafayette, undated; 242924 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Morse -- Miscellaneous Color Photos, undated; 242925 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Morse Photographs, undated; 242926 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Morse -- Supplementary Photos Not in Show, undated; 242927 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Morse -- Chapel of the Virgin at Subiaco, undated; 242928 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Series I: Morse -- Rev. Nathaniel Bowen, undated; 242929 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Series I: Morse -- Dying Hercules, undated; 242930 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Series I: Morse -- Lucretia Morse with Children, undated; 242931 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Series I: Morse -- The Gallery of the Louvre, undated; 242932 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Series I: Morse -- Self-Portrait, undated; 242933 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Series I: Morse -- Contadini Sketch for Chapel at Subiaco, undated; 242934 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Series I: Morse -- Mrs. George Gallagher, undated; 242935 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Series I: Morse -- George Gallagher, undated; 242936 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Samuel Morse -- Paul J. Strati, undated; 242937 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Kahlo/Modotti White Chapel Copy Negatives (1 of 2), undated; 242984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Kahlo/Modotti White Chapel Copy Negatives (2 of 2), undated; 242983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Kahlo/Modotti Exhibit, undated; 242985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography – Cindy Sherman, undated; 242986 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Faces Photographed –- Wegman (Press Only), undated; 242987 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography -– Alice Springs (Press Only), undated; 242988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography – Scott Heiser (Press Only), undated; 242989 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography -– Coplans, undated; 242990 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Faces Photographed -– Nancy Crampton (Press Only), undated; 242991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography -– David Seidner, undated; 242992 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Faces Photographed -– Press Photos Not Used, undated; 242993 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Eva Hesse Photos - 1st Choices, undated; 242994 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Eva Hesse Photos – 2nd Choices, undated; 242995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Portrait Photography – Hujar (Press Only), undated; 242996 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Park Photographs, undated; 242997 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Wonner Photographs, undated; 242998 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Series I: Picasso Photos, undated; 242999 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Series I: Louise Dahl-Wolfe, undated; 243000 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Series I: Two Installations -- Correspondence, undated; 243001 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Series I: Kahlo/Modotti Photographs, undated; 243002 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Series I: Kahlo/Modotti Publicity Photographs, undated; 243003 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Series I: Kahlo/Modotti Negatives, undated; 243004 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Series I: Ottoman Photos, undated; 243005 (Box V:9, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Louise Dahl-Wolfe -- Press, undated; 243006 (Box V:9, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Paul Outerbridge -- Description, undated; 243007 (Box V:9, Folder 3)
  - Series I: AWG Exhibit –- Press Photos, undated; 243008 (Box V:9, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Boldini -– Valentin Abdy Collection, undated; 243009 (Box V:9, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Boldini -– Catalogue, undated; 243010 (Box V:9, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Boldini Photographs, undated; 243011 (Box V:9, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Boldini Photographs, undated; 243012 (Box V:9, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Jean Cocteau -– Press, undated; 243013 (Box V:9, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Bay Area Painting –- Cuear List, undated; 243014 (Box V:9, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Bay Area Painting/Northern California Figs, undated; 243015 (Box V:9, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Bay Area Painting/North California Bischoff, undated; 243016 (Box V:9, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Bay Area Painting –- Joan Brown (Hansen Fuller Golden Gallery), undated; 243017 (Box V:9, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Bay Area Painting –- Joan Brown Olivara, undated; 243018 (Box V:9, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Boldini Photographs, undated; 243019 (Box V:9, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Bay Area Paintings -– Bob's File, undated; 243020 (Box V:9, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Bay Area Painting –- Press Photos, undated; 243021 (Box V:9, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Bay Area Painting –- Park, undated; 243022 (Box V:9, Folder 18)
  - Series I: Paul Wonner Exhibit, undated; 243023 (Box V:9, Folder 19)
  - Series I: Bischoff Photographs, undated; 243024 (Box V:9, Folder 20)
  - Series I: Diebenkorn Photographs, undated; 243025 (Box V:9, Folder 21)
  - Series I: Indelible Image, undated; 243026 (Box V:9, Folder 22)
  - Series I: The Indelible Image Exhibit, undated; 243027 (Box V:9, Folder 23)
  - Series I: Indelible Image -– Press Photos, undated; 243028 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Series I: Sol Lewitt -– Press Photos, undated; 243029 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Labyrinth Exhibit Photographs, undated; 243030 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Precious -- Photos, negatives, and slides, undated; 243031 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Marc Balet and Jack Boulton, undated; 243032 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Action Precision –- Press Photos, undated; 243033 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Series I: Boldini Exhibit, undated; 243034 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Series I: Boldini -– Wildenstein Photographs, undated; 243036 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Series I: Boldini –- Megret Collection, undated; 243035 (Box V:9, Folder 10)
  - Series I: Action Precision Reviews, undated; 243037 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Series I: Modern Redux –- James Stewart Polshek and Partners, undated; 243038 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Series I: Modern Redux -– Bronx Development Center, undated; 243039 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Series I: Modern Redux -– Arquitectunica, undated; 243040 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Series I: Modern Redux -– Color Photos, undated; 243041 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Series I: Modern Redux, undated; 243042 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Series I: Modern Redux, undated; 243043 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Series I: Modern Redux -– Catalogue Photos, undated; 243044 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Series I: Contemporary Indian Art, undated; 243045 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Christmas Card, 1984; 243046 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Contemporary Indian Art –- Press Photos, undated; 243047 (Box 11, Folder 3)